Mina Samy Farouk Zakzouk

El Nozha 2 , Cairo Governorate , Egypt, Cairo, New Nozha • 01276220412 • mina.zakzoukl@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/mzakzouk • https://zo2ka11.github.io/zakzouk/

Software Engineer

2 years of experience. Improved customer satisfaction through proactive problem-solving, developed understanding of object-oriented programming, data structures, algorithms, design patterns, and unit testing.

With 2 years of experience working on small projects and tasks related to the university.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Software Engineering

El Obour Academy • Cairo - Egypt • GPA: B+

Sep 2019 - Jul 2023

Graduation project Grade: A+

WORK EXPERIENCE

Orang Egypt • Cairo - Egypt • Internship

Aug 2023 - Sep 2023

As an intern, I worked as a software tester and unit tester and understood the basics of the software industry and software architecture design

Software Tester

• I developed my understanding of object-oriented programming, as well as data structures, algorithms, design patterns, and unit testing.

Orange Egypt • Cairo - Egypt • Full-time

Mar 2021 - Dec 2022

I was working as technical support for a year and a half, and I was communicating with customers to solve their problems. I also developed an understanding of the field of networking

Technical Support

· Improved customer satisfaction through proactive problem-solving.

AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS

Scholarship 08/2022

Information Technology Institute

PROJECTS

Diagnosing skin diseases using deep learning

Oct 2022 - May 2023

Graduation Project

In the team, I was responsible for creating a model using deep learning, training and testing data, and participating in the website design and analysis.

I worked on TensorFlow framework and created the model using ResNet50

VOLUNTEERING & LEADERSHIP

Google Developer Club

Sep 2022 - Aug 2023

Operation Co-Lead • Cairo

Coach Academy "PST"

Sep 2021 - Sep 2022

Member • Cairo

Member of the problem-solving team and participating annually in the ACPC programming competition for two consecutive years

SKILLS

Technical Skills: Object-oriented programming, Data Structure & Algorithm, Design Pattern, SOLID, SDLC, Docker, Kubernetes, DevOps, Cloud Architect, Linux, Git, CCNA, CCNP

Soft Skills: Work with a team, Problem Solving, Customers Service